{
    "subject": "Lucas_Belvaux",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "La_Raison_du_plus_faible",
    "human_readable": "Lucas Belvaux created La Raison du plus faible.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9242823123931885,
            "question": "Who created the film 'La Raison du plus faible'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7118691205978394,
            "question": "What year was 'La Raison du plus faible' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6789018511772156,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by Lucas Belvaux?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6773609519004822,
            "question": "Where might one find more information about the film 'La Raison du plus faible'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6449933648109436,
            "question": "Are there any awards associated with 'La Raison du plus faible'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6145138144493103,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'La Raison du plus faible' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5693415403366089,
            "question": "How is the film 'La Raison du plus faible' received by critics and audiences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4230342209339142,
            "question": "Is Lucas Belvaux a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33402910828590393,
            "question": "Can you name another film directed by Lucas Belvaux?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32420626282691956,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in Lucas Belvaux's films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lucas Belvaux created La Raison du plus faible.",
            "html": "yago_10401_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another film directed by Lucas Belvaux?",
            "html": "yago_10401_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Lucas Belvaux a filmmaker?",
            "html": "yago_10401_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is the film 'La Raison du plus faible' received by critics and audiences?",
            "html": "yago_10401_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10401_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10401_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10401_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10401_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10401_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10401_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10401_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10401_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10401_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10401_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents contain multiple mentions of Lucas Belvaux and his film \"La Raison du plus faible\", including a detailed description of the film's plot, release year (2006), and director. Additionally, the image details for the film poster also confirm that it is indeed directed by Lucas Belvaux."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the film \"La Raison du plus faible,\" which was directed by Lucas Belvaux. Therefore, the statement that Lucas Belvaux created \"La Raison du plus faible\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}